nakedjuiceclass.com 2013-09-05

# Gilardi & Co, LLC

 Print this page

Protecting the security and privacy of personal information is important to Gilardi & Co. LLC ("Gilardi"). We conduct our business in compliance with applicable laws and regulations on data privacy protection and security. Specifically, Gilardi complies with the Office of Privacy Protection in the California Department of Consumer Affair's Recommended Practices for Protecting Confidentiality of Social Security Numbers [(http://www.privacy.ca.gov/)](http://www.privacy.ca.gov/). 

The policy outlined below explains Gilardi’s guidelines for collection, use, and disclosure of personal information. 

The Information We Collect

Gilardi collects personal information in three ways:   

  * Information provided by a broker or nominee acting on an individual's behalf

  * Information provided by a Company directly involved with the litigation

  * Information provided directly from an individual on a Proof of Claim Form or other similar means

Examples of personal information we collect include, but are not limited to, name, telephone number, e-mail address, street address, social security number and relevant account information. 

In addition, Gilardi collects non-personal information obtained from our web site, such as a user's Internet Protocol (IP) address, Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser software, when and where the user accessed our site, and other information that identifies the computer the user is utilizing. Please read the “Cookies” section below for more information. 

How We Use This Information

The personal information Gilardi collects is used only to the extent it is necessary to complete the claims administration process and when necessary, respond to claimant inquires. Personal information is stored in a combination of paper and electronic files and is protected by security measures appropriate to the nature of the information. 

Non-personal information Gilardi collects is used to determine the number of visitors to our website and provide assistance when monitoring our systems. 

Information collected by Gilardi is not used for marketing purposes or for any purpose other than claims administration. 

Who We Share This Information With

Gilardi does not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We only share information when it is necessary to carry out the claims administration process. 

On a limited basis, we share information with our subcontractors and professional service vendors who assist us in the claims administration process. All subcontractors and professional service vendors are bound by the same privacy obligations as outlined in this policy and only use the personal information to assist in the claims administration process. 

In addition, Gilardi shares personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or as otherwise required by law. 

Security of Your Personal Information

Gilardi is committed to protecting the Personal Information you share with us. We utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

When we transfer sensitive personal data (for example, social security numbers) over the Internet, we protect it using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. 

While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit. 

We recommend you to take every precaution in protecting your Personal Information when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

Cookies

In some cases Gilardi uses technologies, such as cookies, which allow us to make your visit to our website easier, more efficient and more valuable by providing you with a customized experience and recognizing you when you return. 

A cookie is a small coded file on your hard drive to keep track of the pages you have visited. They can only be read by the site that sent them to you, and they cannot search anything else on your computer. The only Personal Information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Accepting cookies used on our website may give us access to information about your browsing behavior, which we may use to personalize your experience and track user traffic patterns, and to merge this info when you register. 

Data retention

Gilardi will not retain your Personal Information longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. 

Children’s Privacy

Gilardi does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from Page 3 our systems. Gilardi encourages parents and guardians to go online with their children. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:   

  * Teach children never to give Personal Information (such as name, address, phone number, school, etc.) unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult.

  * Know the sites your children are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

  * Look for website privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is treated.

Please visit the FTC’s website [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/) for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online. 

General

The Gilardi web site may contain links to information at other web sites. By clicking on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

Gilardi reserves the right to amend this policy without prior notification. 

If you have any questions regarding this policy please contact [**dataprivacy@gilardi.com**](mailto:dataprivacy@gilardi.com)
